## Fayyaz Ahmad

#### Android/Flutter Developer

Studied BSCS From University of Sargodha. Strongly skilled and experienced app development with the vast Knowledge of computer languages. Basic Knowledge about Java, Dart, Android Studio, xml, Flutter. Confident in dealing with customers. Friendly & Dynamic Personality and ability to supervise.

faizikharl7861@gmail.com

03006228806

Lahore, Pakistan

linkedin.com/in/faizi-kharl-388618142 in

Faizikharl7861@gmail.com

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## **Android Application Developer**

3+ Years

01/2019 - Present

# **Android Application Developer**Urban Unit

09/2020 - Present Lahore

Government Sector Orginazation

Achievements/Tasks

- Implement Esri, Google and MapBox services in Android Applications.
- Uipt Sindh Flood Survey Android Application 2022. We Collected over 2.5 million Records.
- Uipt Punjab Flood Survey Android Application 2022.
- Uipt Khyber Pakhtunkhwa Tracking Android Application.
- Uipt Khyber Pakhtunkhwa Integration Flutter Application.
- Uipt Khyber Pakhtunkhwa Property Tax Android Application.
- Uipt Punjab Property Tax Android Application.
- Uipt Punjab Boundry Demarcation Android Application.
- Developed and Designed more than 20 applications in Android and Flutter for Urban Unit.

### **Android application Developer** Versatile Technology

03/2019 - 09/2020

Achievements/Tasks

- Designed, implement and monitor android apps for continuous improvement.
- Cooperate with designers to create clean interfaces and simple, intuitive interactions and experiences.

# Android developer Internship Digicon valley

01/2019 - 03/2019

Achievements/Tasks

- Cooperate with designers to create clean interfaces and simple, intuitive interactions and experience's
- Application Created Dhobi for pakistan user you can see it of google play store.

#### **SKILLS**



#### PERSONAL PROJECTS

University Bus Tracking System (01/2018 - 06/2018)

• Final Year Project.

ExerciseTracker (12/2020 - 02/2021)

• Fiverr Project.

#### **LANGUAGES**

English Urdu
Professional Workina Proficiency Native or Bilinaual Proficiency

#### **INTERESTS**

Movies | Court piece | Agriculture farming

## **EDUCATION**

#### **BSCS**

University of sargodha

08/2014 - 10/2018